How many times did you go today?
今日は何回行った?
I'm going to go crazy.
めちゃくちゃ行きます
I went crazy.
め ちゃくちゃ行った
Is Souch delicious?
スーシュ美味しいかな?
Yeah.
うん
Ah, what an amazing feeling
あ、すごい気持ち
good.
いい
It tastes amazing.
すごい 味わうね
delicious?
美味しい?
There's no way I can swallow all of this.
これ全部丸飲みできるなんていないよ
Yeah.
うん
amazing.
すごい
Ah, wow wow.
あ、 すごいすごい
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
Look here.
こっち見て
Ah, it feels good.
あ、気持ちいい
Is it delicious?
美味しいの?
Oh wow wow wow.
あ、すごいすごいすごい
No one can do that.
そんなの誰もできない
Yeah.
うん
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Ah, amazing.
あ、すごい
Sush
スーシュ
Let's do some kulchan while sucking dick.
ち んぽしゃぶりながら クルチャンで行ってごら
yeah.
ん
Yeah.
うん
Properly.
ちゃん と
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Ah, let's go.
あ、行くぞ
Oh, let's go, let's go.
あ、行く行く
delicious.
美味しい
No taste?
味が来ない?
Yeah.
うん
sweet?
甘い?
ordinary?
普 通?
sweet.
甘い
Strange taste.
不思議な味
It came out.
出た